LEONARDO **IGEL**

A front end developer, focused on building front end applications using React.

Highly motivated and happy to learn new technologies and methodologies. Has experience using React, Redux, as well as NodeJS, Express and Mongodb. Looking a front end development positions, where I could contribute and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team.



Contact







Linkedin

Portfolio



Education

Full stack development course

11/2019 - 03/2020

Netcraft Academy

Learning web development fundamentals, including front end and back end methodologies.

B.A. in Technological Marketing

10/2013 - 10/2016

Sapir Academic College

The studies included courses in business strategies, marketing tools and decision making. During the studies I learned the basics of HTML5, CSS3 and SQL.



Work experience

Chief Security Officer

02/2019 - 10/2019

Check Point Software Technologies Itd

Maintains safe and secure environment for applicants and employees.

Chief Security Officer

01/2018 - 12/2018

US Embassy in Israel

Maintains safe and secure environment for the embassy and its personnel.

Search Engine Advertising (PPC) Manager

01/2016 - 01/2017

Eschar & more

Monitoring and optimizing PPC campaigns using Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Outbrain and Facebook Ads.

0542518474 leoigeltiko15@gmail.com



Work experience

Responsible for direct contact with the clients and making sure their goals are met.



Skills

Front End

Javascript (ES6) HTML5 CSS3 React.js Redux Material-UI **Bootstrap**

Back End

NodeJS Express MongoDB

Marketing

SEO Google Analytics Google Adwords Facebook Ads



Languages

Languages Skills

Portuguese Mother tongue English Fluent Hebrew Fluent Spanish **Proficient**



Personal interests

- Technology and Software development Podcasts.
- Sports and athletics